<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Gabriel Massadas Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://massadas.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Gabriel Massadas Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 18:14:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://massadas.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Logistics Management Software</title>
      <link>https://massadas.com/projects/logistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 18:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://massadas.com/projects/logistics/</guid>
      <description>1. Project Information&amp;rsquo;s During my first year of under graduation, I was contracted by a company to solve problems and speed up processes inside a local logistics company.
The biggest problem in the company was how they handled every waybill, because they were restrained to a single Excel file that stored thousands of Excel functions, automation and waybill records. And because they were just a local company, that meant that they had to integrate with other bigger logistics companies, that sent them every morning what packages they were sending and where does packages needed to be at the end of the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GetCompany.info Repository</title>
      <link>https://massadas.com/projects/companies-repository/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 19:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://massadas.com/projects/companies-repository/</guid>
      <description>1. Project Information&amp;rsquo;s This project was an online database, where anyone could search for Portuguese companies through various ways, including related companies by activities.
This was a side project developed only for personal use. As it was beginning to get indexed by Google it started receiving a lot of daily people searching for companies.
This project was later shutdown and now it is available on Github.
The source code for this project doesn&amp;rsquo;t include any information&amp;rsquo;s about the companies, you have to get it however you want and add it to the database by yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>